import { Question } from "../components/MovieQuiz";

export const officeData: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "What is the name of the company where the main characters work?",
    options: [
      "Dunder Mifflin",
      "Wernham Hogg",
      "Scranton Paper",
      "Vance Refrigeration",
    ],
    answer: "Dunder Mifflin",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the Regional Manager of the Scranton branch at the start of the series?",
    options: ["Michael Scott", "Jim Halpert", "Dwight Schrute", "Andy Bernard"],
    answer: "Michael Scott",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Michael Scott's movie?",
    options: [
      "Threat Level Midnight",
      "Lazy Scranton",
      "Scott's Tots",
      "Goldenface",
    ],
    answer: "Threat Level Midnight",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Dwight's cousin's name?",
    options: ["Mose", "Rolf", "Zeke", "Jeb"],
    answer: "Mose",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Pam and Jimâ€™s first child?",
    options: ["Cecelia", "Philip", "Astrid", "Angela"],
    answer: "Cecelia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the title of the regional manager Michael Scott's self-help book?",
    options: [
      "Somehow I Manage",
      "The Best Boss",
      "World's Best Boss",
      "Management Tips",
    ],
    answer: "Somehow I Manage",
  },
  {
    question: "Who starts the fire in the office?",
    options: ["Ryan Howard", "Dwight Schrute", "Michael Scott", "Pam Beesly"],
    answer: "Ryan Howard",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the annual awards ceremony hosted by Michael?",
    options: [
      "The Dundies",
      "The Scranties",
      "The Scotties",
      "The Dunder Awards",
    ],
    answer: "The Dundies",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Creed Bratton's job title?",
    options: ["Quality Assurance", "Salesman", "Receptionist", "Accountant"],
    answer: "Quality Assurance",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Jim put in Jell-O as a prank?",
    options: [
      "Dwight's stapler",
      "Michael's mug",
      "Creed's keys",
      "Pam's phone",
    ],
    answer: "Dwight's stapler",
  },
  {
    question: "What song does Michael and his nephews perform at the office?",
    options: [
      "Hey Mr. Scott",
      "Lazy Scranton",
      "The Office Theme",
      "Feliz Navidad",
    ],
    answer: "Lazy Scranton",
  },
];
